[
    {
        "set_name": "Sample",
        "created_date": "2025-11-07 00:50:20",
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "Question 1",
                "answer": "Answer 1",
                "progress": {
                    "learned": false,
                    "times_correct": 31,
                    "times_wrong": 19
                }
            },
            {
                "question": "Question 2",
                "answer": "Question 2",
                "progress": {
                    "learned": false,
                    "times_correct": 30,
                    "times_wrong": 19
                }
            },
            {
                "question": "Question 2",
                "answer": "Question 2",
                "progress": {
                    "learned": false,
                    "times_correct": 30,
                    "times_wrong": 18
                }
            },
            {
                "question": "Question 4",
                "answer": "Question 4",
                "progress": {
                    "learned": false,
                    "times_correct": 24,
                    "times_wrong": 21
                }
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "set_name": "Sample 10 Questions",
        "created_date": "2025-11-07 01:34:55",
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "Questions 1",
                "answer": "Questions 1"
            },
            {
                "question": "Questions 2",
                "answer": "Questions 2"
            },
            {
                "question": "Questions 3",
                "answer": "Questions 3"
            },
            {
                "question": "Questions 4",
                "answer": "Questions 4"
            },
            {
                "question": "Questions 5",
                "answer": "Questions 5"
            },
            {
                "question": "Questions 6",
                "answer": "Questions 6"
            },
            {
                "question": "Questions 7",
                "answer": "Questions 7"
            },
            {
                "question": "Questions 8",
                "answer": "Questions 8"
            },
            {
                "question": "Questions 9",
                "answer": "Questions 9"
            },
            {
                "question": "Questions 10",
                "answer": "Questions 10"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "set_name": "QWWDAS",
        "created_date": "2025-11-07 23:34:26",
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "ASDAS",
                "answer": "DASDAS"
            },
            {
                "question": "DASDAS",
                "answer": "DAS"
            },
            {
                "question": "DASD",
                "answer": "ASDAS"
            },
            {
                "question": "ASDASD",
                "answer": "ASD"
            }
        ]
    }
]